PEERAPAHT MACHAITHAT

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Experience

2023

C.P. ALL PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED

Intern at 7-11 at Soi Sukha Prachasan 1 Soi 5

- Working at the 7-11 branch located at Soi Sukha Prachasan 1 Soi 5, in the capacity of an intern.
- I primarily worked at the cashier, handling various cashiering duties.
- Restocking, conducting inventory checks.
- Brewing coffee at All Cafe.
- I also worked at the food place.
- Cleaning and maintaining the cleanliness of various areas within the store.

2021 - 2022

I.C.P. ALL PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED

Intern at 7-11 at Ekkamai

- Working at the 7-11 branch in Ekkamai as an Assistant Store Manager Intern.
- I had the responsibility of assisting the Store Manager in various tasks.
- · Checking and verifying product orders.
- Managing documentation.
- Overseeing the importation of new products and promotional items to increase sales.
- Providing training to employees and interns who have come to work at the branch store.

2019 - 2021 C.P. ALL PUBLIC COMPANY LIMITED

Intern at 7-11 at Maleenont

- Working at the 7-11 branch in the Maleenont in the capacity of an intern.
- I primarily handled cashier duties.
- Organizing, restocking, checking inventory.
- Brewing coffee at All Cafe.

Education

2022 - Present |

2019 - 2022

Panyapiwat Institute of Management

Bachelor's Degree, major DigitalTechnology and Information Technology. GPAX 3.88

Panyapiwat Learning Center Sukhumvit

Certificate of Professional Qualification, Educational Degree in Retail Business.GPAX 3.83



Personal information

Birthday: 15 / 08 / 2547

Age : 19

peeraphatmachaithat.21711@gmail.com

092-812-0600

tub mansion 56/95Chaengwattana Road, Pakkred, Nonthaburi 11120

About me

• I want to step into the field of Full Stack Development as a good starting point different from working in the IT field and develop various skills to become a Full Stack Developer at an expert level.

Skill

: Beginner Java HTML : Beginner CSS : Beginner Cisco : Beginner Javascript: Beginner Node js : Beginner React :Beginner

Language

• English : Basic

Certificate

 The information technology passport examination(IP)

Hobby

Cooking Exercise

Reading novel



าอยกลับ

6552100132 นายพีรพัฒน์ มาใจทัศน์

				ภาคพเค	19/2303				
รหัสวิชา		ชื่อวิชา							
1312102	จริยร	จริยธรรมและมาตรฐานทางเทคโนโลยีสารสนเทศ							
HM60106	นวัต	นวัตกรรมกับการพัฒนาคุณภาพชีวิต							
SO60101	บุคลิ	บุคลิกภาพและสัมพันธภาพทางสังคม							Α
TH60101	TH60101 ภาษาไทยเพื่อการสื่อสาร							3	Α
						ผลการศึกษา	า:ปกติ		
	J	THIS	SEMES	TER	CUMU	JLATIVE TO TH	IIS SEM	ESTER	
C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	ระดับคะแนนเฉลี่ยสะสม	C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	GPAX
12	12	12	46.5	3.88	12	12	12	46.5	3.88

				ภาคการศึก	ษาที่ 1/2565					
รหัสวิชา		ชื่อวิชา								
1311101	พื้นฐ	พื้นฐานเทคโนโลยีสารสนเทศและปัญญาประดิษฐ์								
1311102	คณิต	คณิตศาสตร์สำหรับเทคโนโลยีสารสนเทศ							Α	
1311103	สถิติ	สถิติสำหรับเทคโนโลยีสารสนเทศ							Α	
1312101	เทคโนโลยีดิจิทัลและสารสนเทศในธุรกิจ							3	Α	
1312103	การออกแบบกราฟิกและสื่อดิจิทัลสำหรับอุตสาหกรรมดิจิทัล							3	B+	
1312104	พื้นฐ	พื้นฐานการเขียนโปรแกรม						3	Α	
1312211	1 โครงสร้างคอมพิวเตอร์และระบบปฏิบัติการ							3	Α	
EN60101	N60101 ภาษาอังกฤษพื้นฐาน							2	Α	
						ผลการศึกษา :ป	กติ			
		THIS	SEMES	TER	CUMULATIVE TO THIS SEMESTER					
C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	ระดับคะแนนเฉลี่ยสะสม	C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	GPAX	
23	23	23	90.5	3.94	35	35	35	137	3.91	

				2					
				ภาคการศึกษ	ะ าที่ 2/2565				
รหัสวิชา		ชื่อวิชา							
1301107	โครง	โครงงานทางวิศวกรรมและเทคโนโลยี							Α
1302151	การเรียนรู้ภาคปฏิบัติสำหรับวิศวกรและนักเทคโนโลยี							3	Α
1311104	1311104 การสื่อสารและการนำเสนอทางวิชาชีพเทคโนโลยีสารสนเทศ							3	Α
1312210	12210 การเขียนโปรแกรมเชิงวัตถุข้ามแพลตฟอร์ม							3	Α
1312212	ระบบโครงข่ายและคลาวด์							3	Α
1313301	สาราย การตลาดดิจิทัล							3	В
						ผลการศึกษา	:ปกติ		
	Т	HIS S	SEME	STER	CUMULATIVE TO THIS SEMESTER				
C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	ระดับคะแนนเฉลี่ยสะสม	C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	GPAX
16	16	16	61	3.81	51	51	51	198	3.88

	ภาคการศึกษา	เที่ 1/2566		
รหัสวิชา	ชื่อวิชา		หน่วยกิต	เกร
1312205	การวางแผนทรัพยากรทางธุรกิจขององค์กรโด	ยรวมสำหรับธุรกิจ	3	
1312207	พาณิชย์อิเล็กทรอนิกส์		3	
1312208	ระบบฐานข้อมูลและข้อมูลขนาดใหญ่		3	
1313320	การศึกษาเฉพาะเรื่องทางดิจิทัลเทคโนโลยี 1		3	
EN60206	ภาษาอังกฤษเพื่อการนำเสนอและการสื่อสารในเ	ชิงธุรกิจ	2	
		ผลการศึกษา :ยังไม	เคำนวณ	
	THIS SEMESTED	CHMIII ATIVE TO THIS	CEMECTED	

					Me	การศกษา :ยง เ	มผานาย	и	
THIS SEMESTER					CUMULATIVE TO THIS SEMESTER				
C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	ระดับคะแนนเฉลี่ยสะสม	C.Register	C.Earn	CA	GP	GPAX
14	0	0	0	0.00	65	51	51	198	3.88





To Whom It May Concern

This is to certify that Mr. Peeraphat Machaithat (Certificate no. THIP23S0044), has successfully passed the Information Technology Passport Examination (IP), under the Information Technology Professionals Examination (ITPE) program, jointly organized by Career for the Future Academy of Thailand, and the Information-technology Promotion Agency (IPA) of Japan, on Sunday, April 30th, 2023.

Sirichai Kittivarapong, Ph.D.

Director

S.Kutt

Career for the Future Academy

April 30th, 2023.

Career for the Future Academy

Tel. 0 2644 8150 ext. 81901

Fax. 0 2644 8110